(
"ai_sub_version": "1.11.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
雪花ラミィ生誕３Dヒーローショー
雪花ラミィ生誕３DLIVE『 ホロレンジャー』
Yukihana Lamy Birthday 3D Hero Show
Yukihana Lamy Birthday 3D LIVE 'Holo Ranger'
そっと窓を開けてみる
I softly try opening the window
冬の風がそっとささやく
The winter wind softly whispers
雪が降り積もる街で
In the town where snow piles up
君の面影を探して
I search for your memory
銀色の世界が広がる
A silver world spreads out
静かに夜が更けていく
The night silently deepens
祈りを込めて歌うよ
I'll sing with a prayer in my heart
君に届くように
So that it reaches you
君の銀の庭で
In your silver garden
二人で歩いたあの日
That day when we walked together
今はもう遠い夢のよう
It's like a distant dream now
雪の花が舞い散る
Snowflowers are dancing and falling
冷たい風に吹かれて
Blown by the cold wind
君のことを想っている
I'm thinking of you
いつもそばにいてくれた
You were always by my side
君の銀の庭で
In your silver garden
ずっと忘れないから
I'll never forget
雪の花が咲く頃に
When the snowflowers bloom
また君に会えるかな
I wonder if I can see you again
君の銀の庭で
In your silver garden
二人で歩いたあの日
That day when we walked together
今はもう遠い夢のよう
It's like a distant dream now
雪の花が舞い散る
Snowflowers are dancing and falling
冷たい風に吹かれて
Blown by the cold wind
迫るショッカー 地獄の軍団
Shocker approaches, the army of Hell
我らをねらう黒い影
A dark shadow stalking us
世界の平和を守るため
To protect the peace of the world
ゴーゴー・レッツゴー 輝くマシン
Go, go, let's go! The shining machine!
ライダー（ジャンプ！）
Rider (Jump!)
ライダー（キック！）
Rider (Kick!)
仮面ライダー 仮面ライダー
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
ライダー ライダー
Rider, Rider
ライダー（ジャンプ！）
Rider (Jump!)
ライダー（キック！）
Rider (Kick!)
仮面ライダー 仮面ライダー
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
ライダー ライダー
Rider, Rider
第1話 ヒーロー爆誕！？ 雪花ラミィの旅立ち！
Episode 1: A Hero is Born!? Lamy Snowflower's Departure!
あっちゅ。
Hot.
いや、火薬の量、
Wow, the amount of gunpowder...
間違えて爆発させ過ぎちゃったよ。
I got it wrong and set off way too big of an explosion.
もうせっかくの眉毛が燃えちゃうよ。
Geez, my precious eyebrows are gonna catch fire!
あ、雪民さん、ありがとう。
Oh, Yukimin-san, thank you.
お、みんなー、今日は来てくれてありがとう！
Hey, everyone, thanks for coming today!
そうです。今日はラミィの誕生日です！
That's right! Today is Lamy's birthday!
そして、今年のラミィは一味違います！
And this year, Lamy is a bit different!
今年も体力測定で力をつけてきたけど...
I've been building up my strength with fitness tests this year too, but...
みんな知ってる？なんでラミィがあんなに頑張ってたか。
Does everyone know? Why I was working so hard?
実はね、ヒーローになるためなんだー！
The truth is, it was all to become a hero!
ドドーン！
Ta-da!
でも、ヒーローって言っても色んな形があるじゃん。
But even when you say "hero", there are many different kinds, right?
だから今日は自分だけのヒーロー像を探す旅に出ようと思いまーす！
So today, I'm going on a journey to find my own image of a hero!
ん？なんだ？
Huh? What's that?
いや、やめろー！
No, stop it!
おりゃ！
Take that!
雪民さん！
Yukimin-san!
雪民さん、ラミィを守ってくれたの？
Yukimin-san, you protected me?
さっきもバイク片付けてくれたし、
You even cleared away my bike earlier,
雪民さんは本当に偉いねー。
you're really great, Yukimin-san.
よしよしよしよし。
There, there, there, there.
あ、だいふくもいたの？
Oh, Daifuku, you were here too?
ちょっと、また敵が来ないか見張っといて。
Hey, keep an eye out to see if any more enemies come.
今日はね、色んなゲストを呼んで、
Today, we've called on various guests,
たくさんのヒーローを見ることができるから楽しみだね。
and we'll get to see many different heroes, so I'm looking forward to it!
それじゃ雪花ラミィ、ヒーロー探しの旅に行ってきまーす！
Well then, Lamy Snowflower is heading off on her journey to find a hero!
なんで... なんでまた雪民ばっかり。
Why... why is it always Yukimin?
僕だって... 僕だって...
Me too... I want to...
ガッチャマンの歌
Gatchaman no Uta
誰だ 誰だ 誰だ
Who is it? Who is it? Who is it?
空のかなたに踊る影
A shadow dancing across the sky
白い翼の ガッチャマン
The white-winged Gatchaman
命をかけて 飛び出せば
Risking your life to leap into action
科学忍法 火の鳥だ
The Science Ninja Art: Firebird!
飛べ 飛べ 飛べ ガッチャマン
Fly, fly, fly, Gatchaman!
行け 行け 行け ガッチャマン
Go, go, go, Gatchaman!
地球は一つ 地球は一つ
There is only one Earth, only one Earth
おお ガッチャマン ガッチャマン
Oh, Gatchaman! Gatchaman!
誰だ 誰だ 誰だ
Who is it? Who is it? Who is it?
ビルの合間に忍ぶ影
A shadow lurking between the buildings
赤い血潮の ガッチャマン
The red-blooded Gatchaman
夕日を浴びて 駆け出せば
Running out into the setting sun
科学忍法 火の鳥だ
The Science Ninja Art: Firebird!
飛べ 飛べ 飛べ ガッチャマン
Fly, fly, fly, Gatchaman!
行け 行け 行け ガッチャマン
Go, go, go, Gatchaman!
地球は一つ 地球は一つ
There is only one Earth, only one Earth
おお ガッチャマン ガッチャマン
Oh, Gatchaman! Gatchaman!
ハッ ハッ
Ha! Ha!
Go! Go! Muscle!
リングに 稲妻走り
Lightning streaks across the ring
炎の戦士をてらす
Illuminating the warrior of flames
飛び散れ キン肉ビーム
Fire away, Kinniku Beam!
勝利に向かって
Towards victory!
私は（ドジで）強い（つもり）キン肉マン
I am (clumsy) and strong (so I think), Kinnikuman
走る（すべる）
Running (and slipping)
見事に（ころぶ）
Spectacularly (taking a fall)
ああ 心に愛がなければ
Ah, if there's no love in your heart
スーパーヒーローじゃないのさ
Then you're not a superhero
キン肉マン Go Fight!
Kinnikuman, Go Fight!
ハッ ハッ
Ha! Ha!
Go! Go! Muscle!
嵐の 必殺技で
With a storm of special moves
けちらす超人レスラー
Scattering the superhuman wrestlers
マットに 真赤な薔薇が
On the mat, a crimson rose
今夜も咲くのさ
Will bloom again tonight
私は（ドジで）強い（つもり）キン肉マン
I am (clumsy) and strong (so I think), Kinnikuman
誰もが（誰も）待って（いない）
No one (absolutely no one) is waiting (for me)
ああ 果てない夢を追いかけ
Ah, chasing an endless dream
ああ 果てない夢を追いかけ (Uh~ Uh~ Uh~ Uh~)
Ah, chasing an endless dream (Uh~ Uh~ Uh~ Uh~)
スーパーヒーローになるのさ (Ha~)
I'm going to become a superhero (Ha~)
キン肉マン Go Fight!
Kinnikuman, Go Fight!
私はドジで強い（つもり） キン肉マン
I'm clumsy but strong (I think), Kinnikuman
走る（すべる）見事に（ころぶ）
Running (Slipping), splendidly (Falling)
ああ 心に愛がなければ (Uh~ Uh~ Uh~ Uh~)
Ah, if there is no love in my heart (Uh~ Uh~ Uh~ Uh~)
スーパーヒーローじゃないのさ (Ha~)
Then I'm not a superhero (Ha~)
キン肉マン Go Fight!
Kinnikuman, Go Fight!
微か、后、夕陽
Kasuka, Ato, Yuuhi
聞こえないように 俯く体を
My body looking down, so as not to be heard
誰か包んで…壊れる前に
Someone hold me... before I break
弾き出し嘲笑い 瞳を討つ
Expelling and mocking, striking the eyes
闇への引き金
The trigger to darkness
踏み込む強さより
Rather than the strength to step in
抗う痛みなら
If it's the pain of resisting
誰より前で 食らう Conscience
Facing it at the very front, consuming Conscience
引き千切られたプライドが
Torn pride is a
心に巻くブリザード
Blizzard swirling in my heart
ねえ ここから出してって
Hey, is it okay to scream
叫んでいいの？
"Get me out of here"?
埋もれた声は低い空が
My buried voice, the low sky
いつも救ってくれたね
Always saved it
砕かれた幻想の果てで
At the end of shattered illusions
でもまだ終わらせない
But I won't let it end yet
My heart will doubt...?
悲しみ宿った 花びらに伝う
Sadness dwells, tracing the petals
涙が堕ちた 儚き結晶
Tears fell, fleeting crystals
未来さえ試されて
Even the future is tested
箭にかけて
Staked on the arrow
残った現実
The reality that remains
寡黙に見つめ合う
Staring at each other in silence
夕陽はこの鼓動
The evening sun is this heartbeat
生かしてくれるだろう
It will keep me alive
惑う With the truth
Wandering with the truth
転んだ今日が纏わりつく
Today, having stumbled, clings to me
萎れた感情伏せて
Hiding my withered emotions
ねえ 早く気づいてよって
Hey, is it okay to scream
叫んでいいの？
"Notice me sooner"?
傾いた視界に淀む
Can I distinguish the path
道は見分けられるか
Stagnant in my tilted vision?
ゲームは始まったばかり
The game has only just begun
この世に潜む現在いまを
The "now" lurking in this world
My heart will want...
いらない痛みなんてないんだと
"There's no such thing as unnecessary pain,"
素直な自分足して
Adding my honest self
ねえ ここまで来たよって
Hey, is it okay to praise myself
褒めてもいいの？
For coming this far?
埋もれた声は低い空が
My buried voice, the low sky
いつも救ってくれたね
Always saved it
砕かれた幻想の果てで
At the end of shattered illusions
でもまだ終わらせない
But I won't let it end yet
My heart will believe
魔法戦隊マジレンジャー
Mahou Sentai Magiranger
GO FIGHT! マジマジマジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Magi-Magi-Magiranger
信じてフューチャー
Believe in the future
OK! オーライ！勇気をこの手に
OK! Alright! Courage in our hands
旅立て！
Set off!
君が超えたいものは何？
What is it that you want to surpass?
大空 逆風 昨日の自分
The vast sky, the headwind, your yesterday self
立ち向かう時 揺れ動く
When you face it, you waver
その胸に湧き出すパワー
The power surging in your heart
グリーンランド ピンクストーム
Green Ground, Pink Storm
ブルースプラッシュ イエローサンダー
Blue Splash, Yellow Thunder
レッドファイヤー！
Red Fire!
冒険の始まりさ
It's the start of an adventure
GO FIGHT! マジマジマジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Magi-Magi-Magiranger
限界チャレンジャー
Limit Challenger
勇気という名の魔法を持ってる
Possessing the magic called courage
GO FIGHT! マジマジマジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Magi-Magi-Magiranger
夢見てフューチャー
Dreaming of the future
OK! オーライ！明日をこの手に
OK! Alright! Grasping tomorrow
魔法戦隊マジレンジャー
Mahou Sentai Magiranger
旅立て！
Set off!
君が守りたいものは何？
What is it that you want to protect?
友情 プライド 見えない絆
Friendship, pride, unseen bonds
挫けそうな時 そばにいる
When you're about to give up, they're by your side
笑顔に初めて気がつく
For the first time, you notice their smiles
タウロス フェアリー
Taurus, Fairy
マーメイド ガルーダ
Mermaid, Garuda
フェニックス
Phoenix
5つの手重ねたら
When those five hands overlap
GO FIGHT! マジマジマジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Magi-Magi-Magiranger
限界チャレンジャー
Limit Challenger
勇気が勝利の道を示すから
Because courage will show the way to victory
GO FIGHT! マジマジマジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Magi-Magi-Magiranger
信じてフューチャー
Believe in the future
OK! オーライ！この声よ届け
OK! Alright! Let this voice reach out
魔法戦隊マジレンジャー
Mahou Sentai Magiranger
旅立て！
Set off!
唸る大地 風は吹き抜け
The roaring earth, the wind blowing through
たゆたう水 走る雷 燃える火
Swaying water, running thunder, burning fire
GO FIGHT! (マジマジ) マジマジマジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! (Magi-Magi) Magi-Magi-Magiranger
限界チャレンジャー
Limit Challenger
勇気という名の魔法を持ってる
Possessing the magic called courage
GO FIGHT! マジマジマジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Magi-Magi-Magiranger
夢見てフューチャー
Dreaming of the future
OK! オーライ！明日をこの手に
OK! Alright! Grasping tomorrow
魔法戦隊マジレンジャー
Mahou Sentai Magiranger
GO FIGHT! マジマジマジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Magi-Magi-Magiranger
信じてフューチャー
Believe in the future
OK! オーライ！勇気をこの手に
OK! Alright! Courage in our hands
魔法戦隊マジレンジャー
Mahou Sentai Magiranger
旅立て！
Set off!
第2話 仲間の力！心が導くヒーローのカタチ！
Episode 2: The Power of Friends! The Form of a Hero Guided by the Heart!
うーん
Hmm...
たくさんのヒーローと出会えて力はついたけど、
I've met many heroes and gained strength, but...
なんだかいまいちピンとこないんだよなぁ。
...it still doesn't quite feel right.
ラミィ、悩んでる顔してどうしたの？
Lamy, why do you look so troubled?
あ、かなたん！
Ah, Kanatan!
そうなの。ヒーローってどうあるべきか分かんなくなっちゃって。
That's right. I've become unsure of what a hero should be.
力があるだけじゃだめなんだ。
Strength alone isn't enough.
大事なのは、その力をどう使うかだよ。
What's important is how you use that strength.
かなたん。
Kanatan.
握力だけじゃ、世界は変えられない。
Grip strength alone can't change the world.
人々の心を守るのも、ヒーローの大事な大事な仕事なんだから。
Protecting people's hearts is also a very, very important part of a hero's job.
そっか。力で守れないものもあるよね。
I see. There are things strength can't protect, right?
さ。だから、ヒーローにも強い心が必要なんだ。
Yes. That's why a hero also needs a strong heart.
どんなにピンチになっても、乗り越えるたびにどんどん強くなる心が。
A heart that gets stronger and stronger every time you overcome a crisis, no matter how dire.
さ、僕と一緒に歌って、強い心を掴み取ろう！
Now, let's sing together and seize that strong heart!
うん！
Yeah!
プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure, Pretty Cure
DANZEN! ふたりはプリキュア
作詞：青木久美子 作曲：小杉保夫 編曲：佐藤直紀
DANZEN! We are Pretty Cure
Lyrics: Aoki Kumiko / Composition: Kosugi Yasuo / Arrangement: Sato Naoki
プリティでキュアキュア ふたりは
Pretty and Cure-Cure, the two of us are
プリキュア！
Pretty Cure!
一難去って また一難
Out of the frying pan, into the fire
ぶっちゃけ ありえない！
Seriously, unbelievable!
制服着てても ふたりは
Even in our school uniforms, we're
むちゃくちゃ タフだし
Incredibly tough
お互いピンチを 乗り越えるたび
Every time we overcome a crisis together
強く近くなるね☆
We get stronger and closer!☆
Yeah!
your best! my best! 生きてるんだから
your best! my best! Because we're alive
失敗なんて メじゃない！
Failure doesn't mean a thing!
笑う門に福来るでしょ！
Good fortune comes to those who laugh!
ネガティブだって ブッ飛ぶぅ～！
Negative feelings will be blown away!
生命（いのち）の花 咲かせて！思いっきり～
Let the flower of life bloom! With everything we've got!
(Chu chu chu wa)
もっと バリバリ！
More and more energy!
プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure, Pretty Cure
プリティでキュアキュア ふたりは
Pretty and Cure-Cure, the two of us are
プリキュア！
Pretty Cure!
たまには放課後 ほほんと
Sometimes, after school, just relax
おしゃべり Very time!
And chat, Very time!
ウワサは恋する乙女の
Rumors are the vitamin for
ビタミン剤だもん
Girls in love
闇夜に浮かんだ虹の架け橋
A rainbow bridge floating in the dark night
ここに降りて
Descend here
（ここに降りて） 奇跡☆
(Descend here) It's a miracle!☆
your best! my best! 全力だから
your best! my best! Because we're giving it our all
友情 愛情 サイコー！
Friendship, love, the best!
論より証拠の輝くえくぼ
Action speaks louder than words, a shining dimple
必殺技で ハートキュン！
A finishing move that'll make your heart throb!
瞳に星映して 思いっきり～
With stars reflected in our eyes, with everything we've got!
（瞳に星映して）
(With stars reflected in our eyes)
もっと キラキラ！
More and more sparkle!
プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure, Pretty Cure
プリティでキュアキュア ふたりは
Pretty and Cure-Cure, the two of us are
プリキュア！
Pretty Cure!
プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure, Pretty Cure
（プリキュア Chu Chu プリキュア Sha ba da ba da）
(Pretty Cure Chu Chu Pretty Cure Sha ba da ba da)
（Chu Chu Ah Chu Chu Ah）
(Chu Chu Ah Chu Chu Ah)
明日は明日の風吹く
Tomorrow's wind will blow tomorrow
マジ意味わかんない
I seriously don't get it
今しかできない宿題
Homework that can only be done now
頑張らなくっちゃ！
I've gotta do my best!
真逆のキャラでも あい通じてる
Even if we're total opposites, we understand each other
夢を生きる
Live your dreams
（夢を生きる） チカラ☆
(Live your dreams) Power!☆
Yeah!
your best! my best! 生きてるんだから
your best! my best! Because we're alive
失敗なんて メじゃない！
Failure doesn't mean a thing!
笑う門に福来るでしょ！
Good fortune comes to those who laugh!
ネガティブだって ブッ飛ぶぅ～！
Negative feelings will be blown away!
生命（いのち）の花 咲かせて！思いっきり～
Let the flower of life bloom! With everything we've got!
(Chu chu chu wa)
もっと バリバリ！
More and more energy!
プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure, Pretty Cure
プリティでキュアキュア ふたりは
Pretty and Cure-Cure, the two of us are
プリキュア！
Pretty Cure!
プリキュア～！
プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure, Pretty Cure
(Chu wa)
ありがとう、かなたん。なんとなくヒーローって何かっていうのを掴めた気がするよ。
Thank you, Kanatan. I feel like I've finally grasped what it means to be a hero.
よかった。きっとラミィなら素敵なヒーローになれるよ。
I'm glad. I'm sure you'll become a wonderful hero, Lamy.
その人を思いやる気持ちを忘れずにね。
Just don't forget to be compassionate toward others.
分かった。ラミィなりのヒーロー像、考えてみるよ。ありがとう！
Got it. I'll think about my own ideal of a hero. Thank you!
それじゃ、さらば！
In that case, farewell!
あ、行っちゃった。
Ah, she's gone.
よし！この調子で次に行くぞー！
Alright! I'm going to keep this momentum and move on to the next part!
あ！
Ah!
ごめんね、だいふく。
Sorry, Daifuku.
今忙しいの。
I'm busy right now.
後で構ってあげるから。
I'll play with you later.
あー…
Ah...
なんで？
Why?
なんで僕だけ…
Why only me...
見てくれないんだー！
won't you look at me!
ホロレンジャー 生誕3Dヒーローショー
Holo Ranger: Birth 3D Hero Show
祝福鳥メカ
全長：100メートル
重量：10万トン
Blessing Bird Mech
Total Length: 100 meters
Weight: 100,000 tons
正義はいらない
Justice is Not Needed
時に僕らは理想を語る非凡な才能歌人で
Sometimes we are poets with extraordinary talent who speak of ideals
またはキャピタリズムに屈する傀儡の卑しい恋の子で
Or base children of love, puppets succumbing to capitalism
または幸福が描かれたボードを掲げるデモの一員で
Or members of a protest holding boards depicting happiness
言わば貴方にとっての楽しい法螺吹き野郎のオオカミ少年だ
So to speak, for you, I'm a fun-loving, bragging wolf boy
名声を
Fame,
呈裁を
Appearance,
人生そのものを
Life itself—
潰し合おう
Let's crush it together
恨んで 恨んで 恨んでもたまに悔やんで
Grudging, grudging, even if I hold a grudge, sometimes I regret it
描きたい存在に背中をそそられる
Enticed by the back of the person I want to depict
燃やして 燃やして 燃やしても手が震えて
Burning, burning, even if I burn it, my hands tremble
Who's have to? 堂々 重ねて着込んだ
Who's have to? Proudly, I layered them on
分かって 分かって 分かって 僕の正義を
Understand, understand, understand my justice
無能な怪物を凶器で殺した
I killed the incompetent monster with a weapon
妬んで 妬んで 妬んでいるまま選んだ
Envying, envying, while still envying, I chose
その程度のちゃちな正義はいらない
I don't need such cheap justice
時に僕らは希望を託す聖人じみた歌人で
Sometimes we are saint-like poets who entrust hope
またはマキャベリズムを隠した見てくれだけのお置物で
Or ornaments with just looks that hide Machiavellianism
または全てに噛み付く振りだし特異なエキストラで
Or unique extras who just start out by biting at everything
やはり貴方にとっての楽しい法螺吹き野郎のオオカミ少年だろう
Surely, for you, I'm just a fun-loving, bragging wolf boy
現状の
The current state,
展望も
The outlook,
変貌も
The transformation—
何もかもが無価値なんだ
Everything is worthless
存在を
Existence,
本望を
Long-held desires,
人生そのものを
Life itself—
潰し合おう
Let's crush it together
恨んで 恨んで 恨んでもたまに悔やんで
Grudging, grudging, even if I hold a grudge, sometimes I regret it
描きたい存在に背中をそそられる
Enticed by the back of the person I want to depict
燃やして 燃やして 燃やしても手が震えて
Burning, burning, even if I burn it, my hands tremble
Who's have to? 堂々 重ねて着込んだ
Who's have to? Proudly, I layered them on
分かって 分かって 分かって 僕の正義を
Understand, understand, understand my justice
無能な怪物を凶器で殺した
I killed the incompetent monster with a weapon
妬んで 妬んで 妬んでいるまま選んだ
Envying, envying, while still envying, I chose
その程度のちゃちな正義はいらない
I don't need such cheap justice
時に僕らは思想を諭す英雄的な歌人で
Sometimes we are heroic poets who teach ideology
つまり貴方にとってのカリスマ気取った極悪非道なペテン師だ
In other words, for you, I'm an atrocious swindler acting charismatic
ホロレンジャー 生誕3Dヒーローショー
Holo Ranger: Birth 3D Hero Show
キズナ♡スペシャリティ
Kizuna ♡ Speciality
ねえ、生まれてから今日までの間
Hey, since I was born until today,
どれくらいのごはんで
with how many meals
わたしたちはできてるかな
have we been made of?
毎日ありがとう
Thank you for every day
もし食卓から おいしいが消えてしまったら
If "deliciousness" were to disappear from our table,
ああ、迷わずに
ah, without hesitation,
どこにいたって 何をしてたって
wherever we are, whatever we're doing,
取り戻しにいこう
let's go get it back
あれは記念日の記憶
That's a memory of an anniversary,
何気ないあの味も
and that casual flavor too
忘れたりしない
I won't ever forget
ずっと一緒だよって伝えなくちゃ
I must tell you that we'll be together forever
かならず！
For sure!
守りたいこの味は キミと笑いあう毎日の
The flavor I want to protect is from our daily life laughing with you
いちばん側で照らす あたたかい道しるべなんだ
The warm guidepost shining right by our side
みんなと今を熱くするオモイ 育んでこれからも
Nurturing the feelings that ignite the present with everyone, from now on too
大切に刻もう キズナで結ぶスペシャリティ
Let's etch it with care, a specialty tied by our bonds
ホラ、キミに届くおいしいの中の
Look, inside the deliciousness delivered to you...
たくさんのストーリー
...are many stories.
めぐりめぐって ここにあるって
Coming all the way around to be here...
奇跡みたいだよ
...it's like a miracle.
やくそく！
Promise!
繋げたい今がある
There's a present I want to connect...
キミと分け合いたい未来へと
...to a future I want to share with you.
くじけそうな時も
Even when I'm about to give up...
負けないココロで立ち向かおう
...I'll face it with a heart that won't lose.
みんなの幸せなエナジーが作る
The happy energy of everyone creates...
この日々がうれしいよ
...these days, and I'm so glad.
デリシャスに集まれ
Gather deliciously!
パーティは続いていくべ
The party will continue!
世界中で今も
Throughout the world, even now...
それぞれのストーリー
...each and every story...
ひとりずつができることを
...everyone is doing...
がんばってるから
...their best at what they can do.
かならず！
Definitely!
守りたいこの味は
This taste I want to protect...
キミと笑いあう毎日の
...is from our days laughing together.
いちばん傍で照らす
The warmest guide...
あたたかい道しるべなんだ
...shining right by my side.
みんなと今胸を熱くする思い
The feelings that fire up our hearts together now...
育んでこれからも
...let's keep nurturing them from now on.
大切に刻もう
Let's engrave them deeply...
キズナで結ぶスペシャルティ
...a specialty tied by our bonds.
やくそく！
Promise!
繋げたい今がある
There's a present I want to connect...
キミと分け合いたい未来へと
...to a future I want to share with you.
くじけそうな時も
Even when I'm about to give up...
負けないココロで立ち向かおう
...I'll face it with a heart that won't lose.
みんなの幸せなエナジーが作る
The happy energy of everyone creates...
この日々がうれしいよ
...these days, and I'm so glad.
デリシャスにあつまれ
Gather deliciously!
パーティは続いていくね
The party will continue!
大切に刻もう
Let's engrave it deeply...
キズナで結ぶスペシャルティ
...a specialty tied by our bonds.
第3話 闇を超えて！
ねぽらぼ絆ビームで奇跡を起こせ！
Episode 3: Overcome the Darkness!
Create a Miracle with the NePoLaBo Bond Beam!
やっぱりねぽらぼだね！
It's gotta be NePoLaBo!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ねぽらぼ！ハイ！ねぽらぼ！ハイ！
NePoLaBo! Hey! NePoLaBo! Hey!
大福、やっと来てくれた！
Daifuku, you finally came!
許さない...
I won't forgive you...
許さない！
I won't forgive you!
だ、大福？
D-Daifuku?
やみふく
Yamifuku
まさか、あれは...
No way, is that...?
ラミィにかまってもらえず、負の感情が爆発して...
It's because Lamy didn't pay attention to it, and its negative emotions exploded...
闇落ちした、闇福！
...and it's fallen into darkness, Yamifuku!
そんな！大福、元に戻って！
No way! Daifuku, come back to your senses!
うるさい！
Shut up!
こうなったら、力ずくでも元に戻してあげる！
If it's come to this, I'll bring you back even if I have to use force!
元に戻って！
Come back to normal!
熱い！熱い！熱い！
Hot! Hot! Hot!
やりすぎじゃない、これ？
Isn't this a bit much?
すげぇ... 大丈夫？
Incredible... Are you okay?
ど、どうだ？
H-How's that?
くそっ！
Damn it!
大福！
Daifuku!
あ、ラミィ待って！
Wait, Lamy!
ち、ちくしょう！
D-Damn it all!
かまって...
Pay attention to me...
ヤミィ
Yamie
わ、ラミィちゃんが闇落ちさせられた！
Whoa, Lamy-chan's been turned to the dark side!
これでラミィとずっと一緒だ。
Now I'll be with Lamy forever.
ラミィが相手でも止めるしかないよ！
Even if it's Lamy, we have to stop her!
確かにラミィはタフだしね。まあ、ちょっとくらい痛くても平気でしょ！
True, Lamy is tough. I'm sure she'll be fine even if it hurts a little!
あ、ちょうどいいところに。
Oh, just at the right time.
行くよ雪民、手を貸して。
Here we go, Yukimin. Give me a hand.
雪民さん、行けぇ！そりゃあ！
Yukimin-san, go! Take that!
雪民、ごめーん！あぁ！
Yukimin, I'm sorry! Ah!
行けぇ！
Go!
かまって！
Pay attention to me!
まだだ！
Not yet!
ラー・ミィー
Raaa-Meee-
超ラ・ミィ
Mega Lamy
えー、今度はラミィでかくなっちゃったんだけどー！
Eeeh, this time Lamy has become huge!
仕方ない。あれを使おう。
It can't be helped. Let's use that.
あれ？そっか。よし！
That? Oh, right! Okay!
みんな、力を貸して！ラミィのいいところをたくさん言って...
Everyone, lend us your strength! Say lots of good things about Lamy...
祝福のりメカのパワーを貯めて、攻撃だ！
...and gather power for the Blessing Mecha to attack!
ラミィ！ラミィ！
Lamy! Lamy!
よしよしよし、いい感じ、いい感じ。
Good, good, good. Looking good, looking good.
よっしゃ、このまま観客席のみんなもラミィのいいところめっちゃ言ってって！
Alright, everyone in the audience, keep saying lots of nice things about Lamy!
うちらも言うよ！
We'll say them too!
え？うちらも言うの？
Eh? We will too?
言うの？
We are?
あの、ラミィのいいところ言ってこう。そしたら多分ラミィも元に多分戻る、戻るはず。
Let's say nice things about Lamy. Then she'll probably turn back to normal. She should.
あー、確かに確かに。
Ah, certainly, certainly.
なるほどなるほど。
I see, I see.
いつもの感じね。あ、ねねちから！
The usual vibe, right? Okay, Nene-chi first!
はい！
Yes!
ポルカ！ししろん！
Polka! Shishiron!
よし、行け！
Alright, go!
ラミィちゃんに言いたいことがあります！
I have something I want to say to Lamy-chan!
なーにー？！
Whaaat is it?!
ねねのくだらないLINE、秒で返事してくれてありがとう！
Thank you for replying to my trivial LINE messages in seconds!
え、優しい。
Oh, how kind.
あら、いいじゃない。
Oh, that's nice.
これはちょっといい感じじゃない？
Isn't this a pretty good vibe?
あ、増えてる、貯まってる、貯まってる！
Oh, it's increasing, it's gathering, it's gathering!
じゃあ次、おまる、おまる行け、おまる行け！
Okay, next, Omaru, go Omaru, go Omaru!
ポルカ行け！
Polka, go!
ラミィに言いたいことがあります！
I have something I want to say to Lamy!
なーにー？！
Whaaat is it?!
いつもさ、こんな頼りないうちらのことまとめてくれたり、ツッコミ入れてくれたりしてくれて、本当に感謝してるんだ！
You always keep us together and tsukkomi our unreliable behavior, I'm really grateful!
だからラミィ、お願い、元の姿に戻って！どうだ？！
So Lamy, please, return to your original form! How's that?!
いいんじゃない？
Isn't that good?
おお、来た、来た！
Oh, it came, it came!
あ、溜まってきた、溜まってきた。行け、行け！
Ah, it's gathering, it's gathering. Go, go!
はい次、ししろん行け、ししろん行け！
Okay, next, Shishiron go, Shishiron go!
よし！
Alright!
ラミィちゃんに言いたいことがある！
I have something I want to say to Lamy-chan!
なーにー？！
Whaaat is it?!
いつも、ししろんが小ボケをいっぱいすると全部にツッコミ入れてくれてありがとう！
Thank you for always tsukkomi-ing every single one of Shishiron's small jokes!
来い、めっちゃ来い！いいんじゃない？
Come on, really come on! Isn't it good?
ありがとう！
Thank you!
あ、あともうちょっと、もうちょっと！ねね行け、ねね行け、2個目！
Ah, just a bit more, just a bit more! Nene, go, Nene, go, the second one!
2個目、2個目？そう、2周、2周。
The second one? Second one? Yeah, second round, second round.
えー、ラミィちゃんに言いたいことがあります！
Eeeh, I have something I want to say to Lamy-chan!
なーにー？！
Whaaat is it?!
秒で返事してくれるけど、スタンプで秒で終わらせようとするの、やめてねー！
You reply in seconds, but you try to end it with a stamp in seconds too! Please stop that!
これ下がるんじゃね？大丈夫か？
Won't this go down? Is it okay?
あ、上がるはず！上がるはず、大丈夫！
Ah, it should go up! It should go up, it's fine!
おまる行く、おまる行く、おまる行く！行け！よし！
Omaru is going, Omaru is going, Omaru is going! Go! Alright!
え、え、ラミィに言いたいことがあります！
E-E-I have something I want to say to Lamy!
なーにー？！
Whaaat is it?!
これをきっかけに、初期ラミィからやり直してみるのはどうでしょうか？！
How about taking this chance to start over from 'Early Lamy'?!
バカお前！やめろ！
You idiot! Stop it!
やめろよ、ラミィ！
Stop it, Lamy!
ほらー、ダメだって！逆撫でる！
See, I told you that was bad! You're rubbing her the wrong way!
よし、決めるぞ、決めるぞ、決めるぞ！
Alright, I'll decide it, decide it, decide it!
よし、決めろ！
Alright, decide it!
ラミィちゃんに言いたいことがある！
I have something I want to say to Lamy-chan!
なーにー？！
Whaaat is it?!
いつもだいふくらぼを大切にしてくれてありがとう！
Thank you for always taking care of Daifuku!
おお、溜まったー！
Oh, it's at max!
溜まってる、溜まってる！
It's gathering, it's gathering!
これはどうなるんだ？
What's going to happen?
え、どういうこと？
Eh, what does it mean?
やってくれるんじゃないでしょうか、え？！
Isn't she going to do it for us, eh?!
これは？
This is...?
あ、でもこれはパワーが溜まったんじゃないか？
Ah, but hasn't the power gathered?
よしよしよし、ラミィ、元に戻ってくれ！
Good, good, good! Lamy, come back to normal!
行け、ねぽらぼ絆ビーム！
Go! NePoLaBo Bonds Beam!
元に、戻れ！
Return to normal!
ラミィー！！
Lamy!!
ラミィ！ラミィ！
Lamy! Lamy!
う、う、ラミィは一体...
U-U-Lamy is...
あ、元に戻った！
Ah, she's back to normal!
よかったー。
Thank goodness.
だいふくの力で闇落ちしてたんだよ。
You were corrupted by the power of the Daifuku.
いやでも、正直普段のラミィと全然変わんなかったから。
But honestly, you weren't that different from the usual Lamy.
元に戻ってよかった。
I'm glad you're back.
うん。
Yeah.
あ！え、あれ？おお、だいふく！おお。
Oh! Eh? Oh? Whoa, Daifuku! Oh.
だいふく、ごめんなさい、ちゃんと見てあげられなくて。
Daifuku... I'm sorry. I didn't take proper care of you.
あら、ラミィ...
Oh, Lamy...
他人を思いやる気持ちが大事って教わったばっかりなのに。
I just learned that the feeling of thinking of others is important...
うまくできなくて、ごめんね。
...but I couldn't do it well. I'm sorry.
やっぱりラミィには、だいふくや雪民さんがいないとダメなの。
After all, I need Daifuku and Yukimin-san to be with me.
ラミィちゃーん！
Lamy-chaaan!
だいふく、ずっとずっと一緒だよ。
Daifuku, we'll be together forever, okay?
ホロレンジャー 生誕3Dヒーローショー
Holorenger Birthday 3D Hero Show
完
The End
はい、ということで！
Yes, and with that!
みんな、ラミィの生誕祭、どうだったでしょうかー？
Everyone, how was Lamy's birthday festival?
面白かったー！最高だったー！
It was fun! It was the best!
ラミィ、誕生日おめでとうー！
Lamy, happy birthday!
おめでとうー！
Congratulations!
ということでね、まだ終わりませんよ！
And so, it's not over yet!
何と！
Believe it or not!
重大告知が二つあります！
I have two major announcements!
まずはこちら！
First, this!
じゃじゃーん！
Ta-da!
雪花ラミィ誕生日記念2025グッズ！
Lamy Yukihana Birthday Commemoration 2025 Goods!
ということで、詳しく紹介していきたいと思います！
So, I'd like to introduce them in detail!
まずはこちら！
First, this!
ドン！
Bam!
ド、ドドンドドン、みんなね、やってもらって。
D-du-dun-du-dun, everyone, join in.
はい、まずは、こちら、アクリル、
Yes, first, this, Acrylic...
アクリル、アクリルスタンド！
Acrylic, Acrylic Stand!
テーマはですね、この後紹介いたします、
The theme is, as I'll introduce later...
フード付きタオルを身に付けたラミィの...
...Lamy wearing the hooded towel...
...元気な姿となっております！
...looking full of energy!
みんな、飾ってね！
Everyone, please display it!
続いてはこちら、
Next up is this,
ドン！
Bam!
お揃いトレーナー！
Matching Sweater!
これはですね、サイバー衣装のトレーナーとお揃いのデザインとなっております！
This is a design matching the sweater from my cyber outfit!
みんな、ラミィとお揃いにして着てね！
Everyone, please wear it to match with Lamy!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
ぬいぐるみキーホルダー、ファンタジー私服衣装バージョンということで、
Stuffed Keychain, Fantasy Casual Outfit Version!
ユニレリアのね、あの夏衣装を身にまとった、
It's Lamy wearing that summer outfit from Unirelia...
ラミィのぬいぐるみキーホルダーとなっております！
...as a stuffed keychain!
これをね、身に付けて、いろんなところ、ラミィと一緒にお出かけしてください！
Please wear this and go out to various places with Lamy!
そして、続いてはこちら！
And next up is this!
ドン！
Bam!
雪民フード付きタオルとなっております！
The Yukimin Hooded Towel!
これね、あの、雪民さんの顔がフードになっているタオルね。
This is a towel where Yukimin's face is the hood.
雪民さんがね、そこにおるけど、会話...会話...助かる。
Yukimin is right there, chatting... chatting... that helps.
今後ね、イベントとかあった時に、こういうのをね、身に付けてアピールしてくれると嬉しいです！
I'd be happy if you wear this to show your support at future events!
そして、フルセット購入特典はこちら！
And the full set purchase bonus is this!
雪花ラミィ箔押し複製サイン＆メッセージ入り、
A postcard with a foil-stamped signature and message,
描き下ろしポストカードとなっております！
featuring a new illustration!
みんな、これやって！
Everyone, do this!
イエーーイ！
Yay!
ありがとうございます。ということで、以上、
Thank you. So, that was the...
雪花ラミィ誕生日記念2025グッズでした！
...Lamy Yukihana Birthday Commemoration 2025 Goods!
そして、告知二つ目！
And the second announcement!
新曲となっております！
A new song!
この配信の後、21時から
After this stream, starting from 21:00...
フルアニメーションMVが公開されます！
...a full animation MV will be released!
初めてのフルアニメーションMVとなっております！
It's my first full animation MV!
みんな見てね！
Everyone, please watch it!
各種音楽サイトのリリースはこの後0時から配信されますのでよろしくお願いします！
It'll be on streaming sites from midnight, so please check it out!
ということで、みんな今日はたくさんたくさんありがとう！
So, thank you so much for today, everyone!
ありがとうね！
Thank you!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
ということで、最後に新曲聞いていってください！
And finally, please listen to my new song!
それでは、聞いてください。
Now, please listen to...
無敵☆本気でサバイバー！
Muteki Honki na Survivor!
ギリギリの綱渡り
Walking on a tightrope at the very limit
弱音はポケットの奥
Weakness is hidden deep in my pocket
しまい込んだら ただ進むだけ
Once it's tucked away, I just move forward
こけたって 即リスタート
Even if I trip, I restart immediately
そこからがスタートライン
From there is the starting line
もう止まらないよ
I'm not stopping anymore
迷いなんてもう No No
No more hesitation, No No
不器用でも 前へ
Even if I'm clumsy, forward
萎びてる暇は無し
There's no time to wither away
ハイテンションで行こうじゃん
Let's keep the tension high
無敵☆本気だサバイバー！
Invincible ☆ Serious Survivor!
ゼロからでも何度だって
Starting from zero, again and again
メンタル最強モードです 見ててね☆
Strongest mental mode, so watch me! ☆
限界歓迎チャレンジャー
A challenger who welcomes limits
そう不安なんてさ 笑い飛ばそう
Yeah, let's just laugh off our anxieties
最前線 君次第
On the front line, it's up to you
さあ行こう Ready Go
Now let's go, Ready Go
ついてきてよね☆
Follow me, okay? ☆
トラブルさえ追い風
Even trouble is a tailwind
ピンチもドキドキのスパイス
Pinch is also a heart-pounding spice
“Bring it on!!” 胸を張れ
“Bring it on!!” Stand tall
遠回りも Go Go
Even detours, Go Go
転んでも Try だ！
Even if you fall, just Try!
自分史上 一番へ
To the best ever in my history
アクセル全開 ノンストップ！
Full throttle, non-stop!
無敵☆本気だサバイバー！
Invincible ☆ Serious Survivor!
ブレーキなんてお飾りでしょう？
The brakes are just for show, right?
ハート高鳴りモードです 感じて☆
My heart's in high gear, feel it ☆
完全燃焼フィニッシャー
A full-combustion finisher
誰より強く 夢を叫ぼう
Let's shout out our dreams louder than anyone
最終章 君次第
The final chapter is up to you
さあ行こう Ready Go
Now let's go, Ready Go
置いてかないからっ
I won't leave you behind!
最強☆最愛チームメイツ！
Strongest ☆ Most beloved teammates!
君の声がパワーソース
Your voice is my power source
輝いて 駆けてこう 未来へFly high
Let's shine and run, Fly high to the future
超ハイテンションで行こうじゃん！
Let's keep the tension super high!
無敵☆本気だサバイバー！
Invincible ☆ Serious Survivor!
ゼロからでも何度だって
Starting from zero, again and again
メンタル最強モードです 見ててね☆
Strongest mental mode, so watch me! ☆
限界歓迎チャレンジャー！
A challenger who welcomes limits!
そう不安なんてさ 笑い飛ばそう
Yeah, let's just laugh off our anxieties
最前線 君次第
On the front line, it's up to you
さあ行こう Ready Go
Now let's go, Ready Go
もっともっと ついてきてよね☆
Come with me even more! ☆
みんな、今日のライブどうだった？
Everyone, how was today's live?
ラミィヒーローになれたかな？
Did I become a Lamy Hero?
新曲も今までのラミィにはない、かっこいい曲だったでしょ？
The new song was cool and unlike
anything Lamy's done before, right?
みんなの感想、今日のハッシュタグをつけていっぱい聞かせてね！
Let me hear all your thoughts
with today's hashtag!
そして、この配信のあと21時から、
And after this stream, from 21:00,
新曲「無敵☆本気だサバイバー！」のフルアニメーションMVが公開されます！
the full animation MV for the new song,
'Invincible ☆ Serious Survivor!' will be released!
ついにやってきました！フルアニメーション！
It's finally here! Full animation!
今回のMVには、ラミィの大好きなものがたくさん詰まっています。
This MV is packed with things that Lamy loves.
このライブのあと直接MVに飛ぶようになっているので、みんなこのまま待っててね！
You'll be redirected straight to the MV
after this live, so please wait here!
さて、まだもう少し時間があるから、MVをチラ見せしちゃいます。
Well, there's still a little time left,
so I'll show you a sneak peek of the MV.
どうぞ！
Here you go!
無敵☆本気だサバイバー
Invincible ☆ Serious Survivor
無敵☆本気だサバイバー！
Invincible ☆ Serious Survivor!
ゼロからでも何度だって
Starting from zero, again and again
メンタル最強モードです 見ててね☆
Strongest mental mode, so watch me! ☆
限界歓迎チャレンジャー
A challenger who welcomes limits
そう不安なんてさ 笑い飛ばそう
Yeah, let's just laugh off our anxieties
最前線 君次第
On the front line, it's up to you
さあ行こう Ready Go
Now let's go, Ready Go
ついてきてよね☆
Follow me, okay? ☆
このあと ミュージックビデオ公開！
Music video coming out after this!
ラプラス・ダークネス　白銀ノエル　宝鐘マリン　さくらみこ
天音かなた　尾丸ポルカ　大空スバル　白上フブキ
姫森ルーナ　桃鈴ねね　獅白ぼたん
La+ Darknesss, Noel Shirogane, Marine Houshou, Miko Sakura
Kanata Amane, Polka Omaru, Subaru Oozora, Fubuki Shirakami
Luna Himemori, Nene Momosuzu, Botan Shishiro
＜声の出演＞
尾丸ポルカ　獅白ぼたん　だいふく　やみふく
Polka Omaru, Botan Shishiro, Daifuku, Yamibuku
＜サムネイル＞ 戌神ころね　＜ロゴ＞ saku39
＜映像制作＞ Syamo.G-しゃもじ-
Korone Inugami   saku39
Syamo.G-shamoji-
＜OP映像制作＞ Syamo.G-しゃもじ-
＜背景・観客演出映像制作＞ Syamo.G-しゃもじ-
Syamo.G-shamoji-
＜振付／振付アシスタント＞
桜井節子 (トライエフェクト合同会社)
RIA (トライエフェクト合同会社)　KAZZ
Setsuko Sakurai (Tri-Effect LLC)
RIA (Tri-Effect LLC), KAZZ
＜Music＞
神前 暁 (有限会社モナカ)
＜合同会社 VESSEL LIFE＞
Satoru Kosaki (MONACA, Inc.)
＜株式会社 音響ハウス＞
＜SPECIAL THANKS＞ 雪民
COVER Corp.
Yukimin
雪花ラミィ 生誕3Dヒーローショー
「ホロレンジャー」
Lamy Yukihana Birthday 3D Hero Show
'Holo Rangers'